carfactsdaily.com
In 1908,
In 1908, Henry
1908, Henry Ford
Henry Ford introduced
Ford introduced the
introduced the Model
the Model T.
Model T. The
T. The first
The first car
first car built
car built for
built for ordinary
for ordinary people.
ordinary people. Ford
people. Ford painted
Ford painted every
painted every one
every one black
one black because
black because black
because black paint
black paint dried
paint dried the
dried the fastest,
the fastest, keeping
fastest, keeping the
keeping the assembly
the assembly line
assembly line moving.
line moving. At
moving. At peak
At peak production,
peak production, a
production, a new
a new Model
new Model T
Model T rolled
T rolled off
rolled off the
off the line
the line every
line every 24
every 24 seconds.
24 seconds. It
seconds. It didn't
It didn't just
didn't just change
just change driving.
change driving. It
driving. It changed
It changed the
changed the world.
the world.
Follow at carfactsdaily.com